本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版
嘿查莉  这期视频日记很特殊
Hey Charlie. So this is the very special video diary.
这已经是第五十个了  所以我要确保...
It's the 50th one, that I wanna make sure it's really good for...
哇
Whaa!
-哇  哇  哇  哇  -老爸  老爸  老爸
-Whaa! Whaa whaa whaa! -Dad. Dad. Dad.
-干吗  -老爸  嗨
-What? -Dad, hi.
我在录视频日记  而你却在我后面扮演
I'm recording a video diary and it's a little bit difficult
吉米·亨德里克斯来给我捣乱
with Jimi Hendrix playing behind me.
注：Jiimi  Hendrix:著名的美国吉他演奏家，歌手，和作曲人
能你听出来我在学亨德里克斯
You could tell I was doing Hendrix?
我太厉害了
That's awesome.
总之  这是你第五十个视频日记
Anyway, this is your 50th video diary,
所以我想确保
and so I wanted to make sure...
我进去了  我进去了
I got in! I got in!
其实这是第四十九个
And 49 and holding.
你进去什么了
You got in what?
我进大学了
I got accepted at a university.
你说大学  你要上大学了
A university? You're going to college?
我要上大学了  我要上大学了
I'm going to college. I'm going to college.
PJ  这太激动人心了  是哪所大学  哪所大学
P.J., that's fantastic. Where are you going? Where are you going?
-K.C.U.  -K.C.U.
-K.C.U. -K.C.U.!
K.C.U.  是哪个学校
K.C.U.? What's that?
是堪萨斯城市大学  还是肯塔基中部大学
That's Kansas City university, Kentucky central.
管他呢  反正我儿子考上大学了
Who cares? My boy's going to college.
老爸  K.C.U.大学其实是
Dad, K.C.U. Stands for
“咕唧炸鸡大学”
"kwikki chikki university."
这么说来不是个真正的大学
So not an actual college.
不是  不是  但是这个更好
No no, it's ever better.
这可是去内布拉斯加州奥马哈
It is a two-day management
上两天的管理培训课程唉
training course in Omaha, Nebraska.
-啊  -而且我还可以报销车费
-Ah. -And I got a full ride...
来回的公车费全免
Bus fare both ways.
其实  知道吗  我还以为
Well, you know, I kind of thought
你更想念传统意义上的大学呢
maybe you'd like to go to a more traditional school,
但是  如果你更喜欢
but, you know, if you'd prefer
去那个炸鸡大学两日游的话
to go to a two-day chicken college,
这么说吧
then you know what?
我还是为你感到高兴
I'm happy for you.
谢谢  老爸
Thanks, dad.
别说我自吹自擂啊
And not to toot my own horn,
他们只招收分数前百分之九十的学生
but they only accept the top 90%.
所以只有10%的人进不来
So only 10% don't get in?
我也不知道
I don't know.
他们没和我说这块儿
They didn't tell us that part.
好了  你现在就是咕唧炸鸡大学的学生了
Yep, you're a K.C.U. Man all right.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： sarina
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第十五集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E15  Bye Bye Diary
噢  搞什么
Oh, come on.
嘿  同志们  该轮到谁洗盘子了
Hey, guys, whose turn is it to do the dishes?
要不我们还弄值日表干吗
There's a reason why we have this chart.
当我没说
Never mind.
嘿  查莉  你想帮我洗盘子吗
Hey, Charlie, you want to help me do the dishes?
-好  -你太好了
-Yeah. -That's right. You're my favorite.
给你
There you go.
都放进洗碗机里
Everything goes in the dishwasher.
好的  干得好  查莉
Yes, good job, Charlie.
你干啥呢
What are you doing?
我之前从没有过自己的卧室
I've never had my own room before.
所以当PJ走后  我就把他的东西扔到车库里
So while P.J.'s gone, I'm putting off his stuff in the garage.
哪响呢
Where...?
你好
Hello.
噢  是外婆啊
Oh hi, grandma.
好的  好的  我挺好的
Yeah yeah, I'm good.
是这样的  我现在有点儿忙  您能不能
Listen, I'm kind of busy right now, so could...?
恩  恩
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
好的  好的  那真是
<i>Yeah.</i> <i>Yeah, that's...</i>
噢  盖比  想和外婆打声招呼吗
Oh, Gabe, you want to say hi to grandma?
又不是圣诞节  也不是我的生日
It's not Christmas, not my birthday.
算了
Nah.
其实  他不在家
You know, you just missed him.
但我现在真的有点儿忙  所以
<i>But I'm actually</i> <i>kind of in the middle</i> <i>of something, so...</i>
恩  好的  恩  恩
<i>Uh-huh, yeah, so...</i> <i>Uh-huh.</i>
好的  好的
Yeah, okay.
噢  等等  不如和查莉打声招呼吧
Oh, here. Why don't you say hi to Charlie?
给你  拿住
Here, take that.
-问好  -嗨
-Say hi. -Hi.
嘿  查莉和谁打电话呢
Hey, who's Charlie on the phone with?
-噢  是外婆  -我还是先闪吧
-Oh, grandma. -I'm not here.
嘿  我是PJ
Hey, I'm P.J.
-肉汁  -不用了  谢谢
-Gravy. -No, thanks.
教室里应该不允许吃东西
I don't think we're allowed to eat in class.
噢  不是  不是  我叫比利·格拉夫
Oh, no no, I'm Billy Graves.
朋友们都叫我肉汁
My friends call me gravy.
噢  噢  不错
Oh oh, cool.
你和我一样紧张吗
So are you as nervous as I am?
不紧张
No.
噢
Oh.
我爸现在工作缠身  所以我可以整装待发
My dad owns three franchises, so I'm all set.
这周末我所要做的就是狂欢
All I'm gonna do this weekend is party.
事实上  我已经和汉堡技术学院的美女们
In fact I've already set up a little mixer
建立起了良好的感情
with the girls from hamburger tech.
噢  我听说那是个不错的学校
Oh, I hear that's a good school.
早上好
Good morning.
什么事
Yes?
杂碎教授
Professor Giblet...
应该念做“吉布雷”  你什么问题
It's pronounced "jib-lay." What's your question?
就是刚才那个问题
That was it.
言归正传
Moving right along.
我希望你们每一个人
I want each of you
看看你的右面
to look at the person to your right
再看看你们的左面
and then at the one to your left.
你们中的某人将走出这间教室
One of you will pass this class
成为咕唧炸鸡的经理助理
and become a kwikki chikki assistant manager.
而其他人将会问一个最悲哀的问题
The other will ask the saddest of all questions:
要是我该多好啊
What might have been?
这道题这会列入考题吗
Will this be on the test?
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
PJ·邓肯
P.J. Duncan.
好了  PJ·邓肯  鉴于你如此渴望的想张嘴说话
Well, Mr. Duncan, since you seem so eager to speak,
那你就来说说鸡的各个部位
why don't you tell the class the parts of the chicken?
噢  好的  呃  有鸡胸  鸡腿  鸡翅
Oh, okay. Um, breast, thigh, wing.
我是让你说我们咕唧炸鸡所用的鸡的部位
I meant the parts of the chicken we use at kwikki chikki.
别人知道吗
Anyone?
鸡脖  鸡胗  鸡舌  鸡爪
Neck, gizzard, tongue, feet.
正确
Correct.
当然  如果当切割机出现故障时
And of course when the separating machine acts up,
也许会有鸡的眼珠
the occasional eyeball.
噢  嘿  老爸  欢迎来到盖比小天地
Oh, hey dad. Welcome to Gabe's place.
PJ的东西呢
What happened to P.J.'s stuff?
-谁  -你哥
-Who? -Your brother.
噢  想起来了  他的东西已经远去了
Oh right. His things have been removed.
说实话  屋子收拾的还不错
Actually it's very impressive.
我也想弄弄我的屋子
I may have to do this with my room.
老妈要去哪
Where would mom go?
谁
Who?
好了  我正准备看电影呢
Well, I'm about to watch a movie,
感谢前来拜访
so thanks for stopping by.
等一下  “死亡衣橱”
Wait a minute. "Closet of doom"?
是啊  我听说挺好看的
Yeah, I hear it's supposed to be awesome.
盖比  这是史上最恐怖的电影了
Gabe, this is one of the scariest movies of all time.
你会看见令人毛孔悚然的小丑在屋子里乱蹦
You've got the creepy clown that's jumping around the room.
还有一个小孩被衣橱里的神秘入口
You get the kid that gets sucked into another dimension
吸进了异次元空间
through a portal in the closet.
拜托  别剧透啊
Hello. Spoiler alert.
我只是说说而已
I'm just saying.
知道吗  我也可以娱乐下
You know what? I could hang out.
陪你一起看
I could watch it with you.
好了  我今晚只想独自待会儿
That's all right. I kind of wanted the place to myself tonight.
不如明天吧
Maybe tomorrow?
等一下  PJ明天就回来了
Wait a minute. P.J.'s gonna be back tomorrow.
好了  别找借口了  晚安吧
Well, we tried. Bye-bye now.
鸡翅  鸡翅  鸡头  鸡爪
Wing, wing, head, foot.
-嘿  PJ  -嘿  老兄
-Hey P.J. -Hey man.
-哥们  你干嘛呢  -学习
-Dude, what are you doing? -I'm studying.
学习  拜托  老兄  今天可是到这里的第一个晚上
Studying? Come on, bro, it's our first night.
我知道  但明天有考试
I know, but we have finals tomorrow.
老兄  当你双鬓斑白时
Dude, when you get older,
你难道希望  回首在大学的两天时光
do you want to look back at your two days in college
只能说出这番话“我把时间全用来学习了”
and say, "all I did was study"?
那我就休息五分钟
I guess I could take a five-minute break.
-好的  -好的
-Yes. -Yeah.
派对
Party!
泰迪
Teddy.
怎么了
Yeah?
你的笔记本电脑是不是丢了
Have you been missing your laptop?
是啊  我一直在找呢
Yes, I've been looking all over for it.
找到了
Found it.
不要  不要  不要
No. No no no no.
也许还能用
Maybe it'll be okay.
看来报废了
Or not.
复活吧  复活吧  复活吧
Please work, please work, please work.
笔记本电脑怎么会在洗碗机里呢
How did it get in the dishwasher anyway?
肯定是在我和外婆打电话的时候  查莉扔进去的
Charlie must have put it in there while I was talking to grandma.
拜托  启动  拜托  启动
Come on, boot up. Come on, boot up.
-拜托  启动  -泰迪  泰迪  淡定  淡定
-Come on, boot up. -Teddy, Teddy, Teddy, stop it, stop it.
别难过了  我们再给你买个新的
It'll be okay. We'll get you a new one.
不成  老妈  你不明白的
No, mom, you don't understand.
所有的视频日记都在里面呢
All of my video diaries were on here.
宝贝  我还以为都在你的摄像机里呢
Honey, I thought they were in your camera.
没有  我把它们存电脑里了
No no, I put them on my computer
就是为了妥善保存
for safekeeping.
噢  宝贝  宝贝  别难过了
Oh, honey, honey, I'm so sorry.
整整两年的心血  全进下水道了
It's two years' worth of video diaries just down the drain.
也算用洗碗机给漂白干净了
Well, through the rinse cycle anyway.
噢  别这样  别这样
Oh, now come on, come on.
你可以再录更多的视频日记啊
You'll make more video diaries and it'll all be okay.
-算了  我以后也不再录像了  -为什么
-No, forget it. I'm not making any more. -Why not?
如果查莉不能从第一集看起
If Charlie can't watch them from the beginning,
那还有什么意义
then what's the point?
别这样  别这样  你还要给她好多的建议
No no no, you were giving her such great advice
关于如何处理生活  感情和家庭
about how to deal with life and relationships and her family.
她会需要这些建议的
She's gonna need that.
亲爱的  我都要抓狂了
Honey, I'm only gonna get crazier.
不了  她会自己悟出那些问题的答案的
No, she's just gonna have to figure it out for herself.
我不会再录视频了
I'm done with the video diaries.
真是可惜
It's such a shame.
她为视频日记付出了这么多
She worked so hard on those.
而且里面还有我的很多镜头
And I was in so many of them.
看见了吗  约翰尼
<i>See, Johnny?</i>
这个小丑娃娃是死的
<i>The clown doll</i> <i>isn't alive.</i>
好吧  爸爸
<i>Okay, dad.</i>
但是再检查一遍衣橱吧
<i>But check the closet</i> <i>one more time.</i>
好的  小鬼
<i>Sure, sport.</i>
看  这根本就没有  啊啊啊
<i>See? There's nothing to...</i> <i>Arghh-hh!</i>
没事的  可可  这只是个电影
It's okay, cocoa. It's only a movie...
但恐怖的吓人啊
A really scary movie.
来吧  查莉  你今晚睡在PJ的床上
Come on, Charlie. You're gonna sleep in P.J.'s bed tonight.
过来
Come on.
好了
Okay.
怎么回事
What's going on?
呃  是这样的
Um, well,
查莉哭了
Charlie was crying.
我怎么没听见
I didn't hear anything.
但是我听见了
Well, I did.
而且她看起来是受到惊吓了
And she sounded very very scared.
所以我觉得让她和我睡一起  会让她感到安全些
So I thought she'd feel safer sleeping in here with me.
查莉受到惊吓了
So Charlie was scared?
老爸  我知道现在有点迟了  但是今晚查莉和我一间房
Dad, I know it's late, but Charlie's stay with me.
好吧  那个
All right, well,
感谢尽到一个好哥哥的责任
thanks for being such a good Big Brother
这么突然唐突  肯定有鬼
all of a sudden.
小意思
No problem.
在盖比的小天地  就是这么做的
That's how we roll here at Gabe's place.
亲爱的  今天几月几号啊
Honey, what's today's date?
2026年1月7号
January 7th, 2026.
看看我  我又写成了2025年
Look at me. I'm still writing 2025.
查莉·邓肯
Charlie Duncan,
你应该一小时前回家的
your curfew was an hour ago.
管他呢
Whatever.
别这么和我们说话  小太妹  给我把口香糖吐出来
Don't you whatever us, young lady. And spit that gum out.
没问题
You got it.
噢  通知你们下  我退学了
Oh, by the way, I quit school today.
-你什么  -我要和男朋友私奔
-You what? -And I'm running away with my boyfriend.
你和斯内克私奔了
You're running away with Snake?
只要他刑满释放  我们就私奔
As soon as he gets out of jail.
我就费解了  查莉
I don't get it, Charlie.
你虽然长得像泰迪  但是内心和她真是大相径庭
You look so much like Teddy, but you're so different.
噢  又是泰迪  泰迪  泰迪
Oh, Teddy Teddy Teddy.
我听够了那个窝囊废的名字
I'm so sick of hearing about that clump nugget.
嘿  嘿  嘿
Hey hey hey hey.
不许这么说科罗拉多州州长
Do not talk that way about the governor of Colorado.
我管她作甚  她又没为我付出过什么
Why should I care about Teddy? What's she ever done for me?
像是泰迪刚飞过来了
That sounds like Teddy now.
我走了
I'm out of here.
嗨  老妈  嗨  老爸
Hi mom. Hi dad.
二老可好啊
So how are you guys?
那个  不怎么好
Well, not so good.
查莉又不听管教了
Charlie's out of control again.
我就知道会这样的
I knew this would happen.
要是我没放弃录那些视频日记该多好啊
If only I hadn't given up on those video diaries.
宝贝  不要自责了
Honey, you can't blame yourself.
不  这是实话  全是我的过错
No, it's true. It's all my fault.
全是我的过错  全是我的过错
It's all my fault. It's all my fault.
真是的  我不能这样对待查莉
No, I can't do that to Charlie.
但科罗拉多州州长这段  还不赖
Governor of Colorado... Not bad.
-好了  老兄  准备好了吗  -好了  喂吧
-All right, dude, are you ready? -Yeah, sauce me.
天啊  不错的辣酱
Man, that's good hot sauce.
老兄  我都可以喷火了
Dude, my mouth's on fire.
好了  老兄  和你说吧  我要回去学习了
All right, dude, you know what? I gotta get back to studying.
老兄  那些汉堡技术学院的美女可刚到这里
Dude, the girls from hamburger tech just got here.
PJ  这是帕蒂  帕蒂和帕蒂
P.J., this is Patty, Patty and Patty.
欢迎来到派对  派对和派对
Welcome to the party, party and party.
你大半夜的把我叫醒干吗
What did you get me up in the middle of the night for?
老妈  我做了个恶梦
Mom, I had a terrible dream.
十五年后你和老爸都在这里
It was 15 years into the future and you and dad were there.
我看起来如何
How did I look?
挺美的
Really good.
继续
I'm listening.
查莉长大后染了个粉色的头发  还有个叫斯内克的男友
So Charlie had pink hair and this boyfriend named Snake.
好了  好了  好了  先打住
Okay okay okay, hold on.
我到底有多美
How good did I look?
美艳  总之
Fabulous. Anyway,
我知道如何拯救这些视频日记了
I know how we can save the video diaries.
我们要再造它们
We're gonna recreate them.
今晚就造吗
Tonight?
是啊
Yes.
不全部补齐所有视频  我是不打算睡觉的
I'm not gonna be able to sleep until we get them all done.
来吧  开工了
Come on, let's get going.
嗨  查莉  我是你姐  泰迪
Hi Charlie. It's your big sister Teddy here.
而我录制这个视频就是为了帮助你能够在这个
And I'm making this video diary to help you survive
独一无二的家庭里生存
our special family.
好了  大功告成  录完一个了  还剩四十九个
Okay, perfect. One down, 49 to go.
宝贝  你还没说“好运喽  查莉”呢
Honey, you didn't say "good luck, Charlie."
呃
Grr!
所以盖比的朋友杰克对老妈说
So then Gabe's friend Jake said to mom,
“你太老了  你玩不了呼啦圈”
"you can't do the hoops. You're too old."
所以老妈就回应他说
So mom said...
看老娘我的厉害  杰克
In your face, Jake!
记得以后不要把朋友带咱家里来玩
Make sure to have your playdates at your friend's house.
好运喽  查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
如果你的奶嘴曾掉进过花瓶里
And if you ever drop your binky in a vase,
祝我好运吧  查莉
wish me good luck, Charlie.
这条建议好像很垃圾啊
<i>That one seems</i> <i>kind of lame.</i>
才不呢  的确发生过这类的事情
Yeah, well, it happened.
好了  查莉  你的首次宠物店之行
Well, Charlie, your first trip to the pet store
似乎进行的不太顺利  在我们没盯住你的时候
didn't go so well. When we weren't looking,
你往老妈的皮包里放了点儿东西  一只兔子
you put a little something in mom's purse... a bunny.
好了  别弄了  太假了
Okay, wait, stop. This isn't working.
这一看就是达布尼太太的猫戴了双兔耳朵
That's so obviously Mrs. Dabney's cat with bunny ears.
现在是凌晨两点
It's 2:00 in the morning.
你想让我再去趟全天营业的兔子商店吗
You want me to run the all-night bunny store?
我对于你的态度相当的气愤
I really don't appreciate your attitude.
嘿  别这么和我说话  我才是那个
Hey, don't snap at me. I'm the one
跳上围墙抓猫的人
who jumped the fence and nabbed the cat.
成了  算了  在达布尼太太发现之前
All right, forget it. Let's just get him back
赶紧把猫还回去吧
before Mrs. Dabney notices.
快关灯  快关灯
Get the lights. Get the lights.
只是部电影  只是部电影
It's just a movie. It's just a movie.
噢  噢
Oh! Oh!
查莉  上床睡觉去
Charlie, go back to bed.
把那个吓人的小丑也带走
And take that evil clown doll with you.
查莉  你听见了吗
Charlie, did you hear that?
又是这声音
There it is again.
查莉  快醒醒
Charlie, wake up.
嘿  嘿  嘿  怎么了
Hey hey hey, what's the matter?
他们带走了查莉  查莉被那神秘的入口给吸走了
They got Charlie! She's been sucked into the portal!
-什么  -查莉在死亡衣橱里
-What? -She's in the closet of doom!
不要啊  老爸  他们也会带走你的  不要啊
No, dad, they'll get you too. Don't.
噢
Oh.
好了  我的小恶魔
All right, my little monster.
知道吗
You know what?
我要把你放回你自己的床上
I think I'm gonna put you back in your own bed.
什么  你不能丢下我一个人在这里
What? You can't leave me in here alone.
那你愿意睡在鲍伯与艾米的小天地吗
Would you rather sleep at Bob and Amy's place?
我可以吗
Could I?
好吧
All right.
来不来
Are you coming?
我这两个小宝贝
My two little babies.
时间到
And time.
放下笔了  把卷子向前传
Pencils down. Pass your papers forward.
咕唧炸鸡  咕唧炸鸡
Kwikki chikki, kwikki chikki.
我现在就判你们的考试卷子
I will now grade your final examinations.
判完了
Done.
你们都过关了
You've all passed.
好耶
Yes!
肃静  这又不是多大的成就
Quiet. It's not that big an accomplishment.
好了  开始毕业典礼
All right, graduation ceremony.
哈哈
Ha ha.
现在  我非常荣幸的
It is now my honor
向大家请出我们的演讲嘉宾
to present our commencement speaker,
第268号连锁店经理
the manager of franchise #268,
弗雷德
Fred.
很难相信二十年前
It's hard to believe that 20 years ago
我就坐在你们现在的位置上
I sat right where you are now.
我同样是个高中学生
I too was a High School student
一个即将步入这个令人兴奋的世界中的
about to enter the exciting world
咕唧炸鸡经理助理
of kwikki chikki assistant management.
哇
Wow.
这个职位给予了我太多的东西
This career has provided me with so many things,
比如住在家里车库上的房间里
like a room over my parents' garage
一个星期可以开三天车
and the use of the car three days a week.
我曾后悔过没娶妻生子
Do I regret not having a wife
甚至养只宠物吗
<i>or kids</i> <i>or even a pet?</i>
从没有过
Not for a moment.
你也不会有的
And neither will you,
只要你为咕唧炸鸡工作后
after you go to work for kwikki chikki
你会一直呆在这里
and stay there
直到永远
forever and ever.
不要
No!
No.
刚才离开的是PJ·邓肯
There goes P.J. Duncan.
他很笨  他很懒
He was stupid. He was lazy.
但他是这所大学的历史上
But he's still the best student
最优秀的学生
this university ever had.
嘿
Hey.
你对你老妈做了什么
What did you do to your mother?
我刚发现她在厕所睡着了
I just found her asleep on the toilet.
噢  我们挑灯夜战呢
Oh, we stayed up all night
重新录制查莉的视频日记
remaking Charlie's video diaries
直到关了灯来躲避达布尼太太的视线
when we weren't hiding in the dark from Mrs. dabney.
嘿  大家好
Hey, everybody.
嘿  怎么样啊  大学生
Hey, how is it going, college boy?
那个  我成功了  我毕业了
Well, I did it. I graduated.
恭喜啊  前途光明了吧
Congratulations. The future's all set, huh?
没有  没有
No. No, it's not.
为什么
What?
老爸  我认为
Dad, I think...
我认为我的个人价值要高于咕唧炸鸡这份工作
I think I want something more than kwikki chikki.
我想去一所名副其实的大学
I think I want to go to a real college.
好啊  如果你真想如此
Okay, if that's what you want.
嘿  听着  不管你做出什么决定
Hey, look, whatever you decide...
我都支持你
Fine with me.
噢  泰迪
Oh, Teddy.
泰迪  我差点忘了
Teddy, I almost forgot.
我拿错笔记本电脑了  这是你的
I took your laptop by mistake.
你什么
You what now?
抱歉  我拿错了  它们看起来都一样
Sorry, it was a mistake. They just look alike.
这意味着我的视频日记还健在  并没有毁了
That means my video diaries are okay. They're not ruined.
毁了
Ruined?
我笔记本电脑怎么了
What happened to my laptop?
一个有趣的故事
A cute story.
呃  现在有趣了
Um, well, now it's cute.
噢  PJ
Oh, P.J.!
-你回来了  -喔  我回来了
-You're back! -Whoa. Yeah.
噢  我太想你了  求求你不要再离开这个家了
Oh, I missed you so much. Please don't ever leave home again.
好吧  我不会的
Okay, I won't.
嘿  为什么我的东西全在车库里
Hey, why is all my stuff in the garage?
噢
Oh.
呃  一个有趣的故事  呃
Um, a cute story. Um...
嘿  查莉
Hey Charlie.
我终于有机会
So I'm finally getting the chance
来录制你的第五十个视频日记了
to do your 50th video diary.
而我想让它
And I want to make it...
我想
I want to...
我想让它意义非凡
I want to make it really special.
泰迪  泰迪
Teddy, Teddy.
好运了  查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
嘿  盖比  盖比  那是什么
Hey, Gabe, Gabe, what is that?
噢  那是查莉
Oh, that's just Charlie.
她在闹着玩  想吓吓咱俩
She's messing around, trying to scare us.
这个小捣蛋鬼
That little scamp.
我  我  我觉着这不像是查莉
I... I... I don't think that's Charlie.
让我看看
Let's see.
哇  哇  哇  你们又在闹什么
Whoa whoa whoa, what is going on in here?
老爸  衣橱里  有蹊跷
Dad, in the closet... Something horrible.
一个通向异次元空间的入口
It's a portal to another dimension.
噢  饶了我吧
Oh, give me a break.
爸  爸  爸
<i>Dad, dad, dad.</i>
爸  爸
<i>Dad! Dad!</i>
嘿  在盖比小天地里  一切皆有可能
Hey, anything can happen at Gabe's place.